(Sheldon:)It was only to keep our core
body temperatures from plummeting.
(Howard:)-He's speaking about it.
-For me it was a bonding moment.
(Howard:)Sheldon, you remember
the first few weeks...
(Howard:)...we were looking for magnetic monopoles
and not finding anything...
(Howard:)...and you were acting
like an obnoxious giant dictator?
I thought we were gonna be gentle
with him.
That's why I added the "tator."
And when we finally got
our first positive data...
(Howard:)...you were so happy.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. In the world of emoticons,
I was colon, capital D.
Well, ahem, in actuality,
what your equipment detected...
(Howard:)...wasn't so much evidence
of paradigm-shifting monopoles...
...as it was static from the electric
can opener we were turning on and off.